The thing is, what did they do in the first place,
that they're in this, what you call, open-air prison?
Great question, what did they do to deserve being occupied?
Well, here's the thing,
because the Islamic Republic in Iran
is using them as a tool.
What has Iran got to do with this?
As a tool for their Islamic expansion.
When did the Islamic, hold on, hold on,
when did the Islamic Republic of Iran,
you're Iranian-American, I believe.
Yes, I am.
When was the Islamic Republic of Iran founded?
1979.
When was Gaza occupied by Israel?
19, well, the very first time.
67.
67, yeah.
So, can we do the math together?
12 years before the Islamic Republic of Iran existed,
Israel was oppressing, occupying,
dispossessing the people of Gaza.
So your argument makes no sense.
And were there any terrorist organizations at the time?
The PLO was considered a terrorist organization
by the entire Western world.
All right, so, what's Hamas there?
Hamas did not exist until the 1980s.
Exactly, my point is, after the Islamic Republic came,
it became chaotic, because the Islamic Republic
started to use the so-called innocent Palestinians
for their own ends.
So-called innocent Palestinians?
You don't think Palestinians are innocent?
Not all of them.
But what about the 17,000 children who were killed?
They're doing the same.
17,000 children were killed.
Were they not innocent?
Who's responsible for that?
Israel.
No, Hamas is responsible.
Hamas is responsible for hiding in hospitals
and making tunnels underneath those hospitals.
So when children are shot in the head by Israeli snipers,
Israeli snipers aren't responsible for that?
Look, it's a simple question.
Here's the problem.
When Israeli snipers shoot Palestinian children in Gaza
in the head, as eyewitness testimony
and doctor's testimony proves,
that's not the fault of the Israeli snipers.
This is the problem.
Because then you have a problem.
The problem is you won't answer the question.
I'll ask you a third time.
When Israeli snipers shoot Palestinian children
in the head, is that not the fault of Israeli snipers?
You gotta let me finish.
No, you gotta answer the question.
Fourth time.
When Israeli snipers shoot Palestinian children
in the head.
I will get to your answer.
We're running out of time.
I need to know what you think about innocent children.
Because I will get to your answer.
Because what you said was pretty outrageous.
You said so-called innocent Palestinians.
For the fifth time,
when Palestinian children are shot in the head
by Israeli snipers, is that not the fault
of Israeli snipers?
What did those children do?
What did they do?
You tell me, did the children deserve
to be shot in the head?
Because the problem is over there.
You know millions of people are watching you say
they're justifying the killing of children.
They start brainwashing children at a very young age.
So you support sniping children in Gaza?
Look.
Do other people here support sniping children in Gaza?
Is that a conservative position now?
What if they're wearing a suicide vest?
They weren't.
Well, what if they are?
They're not, though.
What if they are?
I have friends who went there.
Doctors went to Gaza.
American doctors.
They came back as if we were multiple children.
What if they're hell-bent?
What if they're hell-bent on killing you and your family?
A 10-year-old child, an eight-year-old child,
a six-year-old child?
Because, like I said,
you're sitting on live television
where millions of people are gonna see
your neighbors, your friends.
You support the killing of children.
Millions of people don't know what's going on.
Even your fellow right-wingers are saying,
don't go this far.
White genocide, sure, but don't advocate killing kids.
Millions of people don't understand
the brainwashing that is going on
in the Islamic Republic and in Palestine
to create this hatred.
You're obsessed with Iran so much
that you're supporting the killing
of Palestinian children who never harmed you
or any other Israeli.
That's insane.
Look.
And the fact that you support Trump's ethnic cleansing
now doesn't surprise me.
I didn't say ethnic cleansing.
I said cleansing of the land.
All right, pause.
Because you need to cleanse the land
from all the total crimes.
I'm sure Slobodan Milosevic
said similar stuff. Pause.
You've been voted out.
Please return to your seat.